# Guillermo Martínez

Hostal de la Pega, 7 Montcada i Reixac 08110, Barcelona

+34 695619727

guillemmartinezconejos@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/guillemmc

I am passionate about creating and developing apps, both mobile and web. I like knowing that thanks to my knowledge I can help ideas become true. That is why since I finished my studies I have focused on software development, and my goal is to continue growing, training, and improving my skills in this field.

I am a curious, cheerful, responsible, and disciplined person. I have experience working in both, teams and solo. Moreover, I count quite a bit of remote working experience. I believe that a good atmosphere in the workplace is the key to be active and motivated, that is why I always try to be in good humor and giving the best of me.

# Professional Experience React (.js & Native) developer, Ulabox.com (MAR 2021 - Present ) Barcelona & Remote Maintenance and development of both, website and mobile app.

- · React.is, React Native, Redux, Sagas & Next.is.
- · Jest, Flow, Lint, Jenkins, Travis & GIT.

### React Native Mid-Level, GooApps (OCT 2020 - FEB 2021) Remote

- · Implement apps from scratch until deployed in the stores.
- Maintenance of existing apps.
- · Reviewing and controlling the quality of the code.
- Meetings with clients to get to know the needs.
- · Backoffice web development to manage the data.

### Software Developer, INTERIORVISTA (AUG 2018 - SEP 2019) Barcelona, Spain

When I returned home I came back completely to the front-end team where I was working with the newest technologies, but not for long. After some months they assigned me to the algorithm development team. I started working with C++ and I was doing complete different stuff, but always helping the front-end team if needed.

I have evolved a lot in this company and I have worked in very different roles (and pretty successfully must say), and I think that this fact defines me pretty good. It defines me because of my ability to get used to changes, to learn new technologies and face new challenges. I learned plenty of different things at the university and this company gave me the option to improve my skills on them.

### Software Developer, INTERIORVISTA (FEB 2017 - MAR 2018) Remotely, Australia

At one point I realized that my career would need something else and I decided to move to Australia (Gold Coast) to master my English for one year and a half. INTERIORVISTA offered me the awesome opportunity of keeping working together, so I picked up a laptop and I continued working for them from the other side of the world.

My role while I was there changed a little bit, I still was int the front-end development team, but they assigned me one man team as well. I was moved to 3D maintenance. So at that time I was half time doing front-end and the other half working with Unity.

## FrontEnd Developer, INTERIORVISTA (JAN 2016 - FEB 2017) Barcelona, Spain

At INTERIORVISTA I started working as a web developer, when I started working the technology used was Angular II but soon we moved to React.js. Working in this role I earned experience in responsible website development and I worked for the first time with Google Analytics.

Working there I learned the importance of GIT and how useful an Agile (we used SCRUM) methodology can be for you team.

### FullStack Developer, ESADE Alumni (NOV 2014 - JAN 2016) Barcelona, Spain

In ESADE Alumni I did my internship during the end of my university years. Working there we made use of technologies such as PL/SQL by Oracle, HTML Javascript and CSS.

#### **Education**

# Diploma of Project Management en Entrepreneur Education, Gold Coast, Australia (2017 - 2018)

Thanks to this diploma I learned the basics on project management, so it gave me the skills to manage and motivate a team if needed in the future.

# Multimedia Engineering Degree La Salle (Universidad Ramón Llull) Barcelona, España (2011 - 2016)

At university I learned a lot about IT in all its forms, I learned basics on things such as web development, mobile development, 3D animation and modeling, video games, video editing and visual effects, image and signal processing, communications, music creation, etc.

### **Other Experience**

### Cook, Sunshine Village Ski Resort (OCT 2019 - MAR 2020) - Banff, Canada

I was cooking in a kitchen of an Italian restaurant, I do everything in there, form cleaning dishes to cook pasta, pizzas making sandwiches preparing sauces or doing the expo of the kitchen.

### Cook, Delaware North (MAR 2018 - MAY 2018) - Gold Coast, Australia

Preparing meals in the cold kitchen.

Chopping + peeling.

Cooking with in huge grills, fryers and ovens.

#### **Curses**

React Native: Complete course on Udemy.com about developing mobile apps.

Apps Development: Online course by Google Activate.

**CCNA1:** La Salle - URL, 2013-2014 (university recognized by CISCO)

3ds MAX level 3 - Animation: La Salle - URL, 2012-2013

#### **Degree Thesis**

To develop my degree thesis (and conclude my university studies), I collaborated with the university to develop a mobile app (more exactly for iOs devices). I did not know much about that kind of programming, but my willing to learn and develop a beautiful project made me to ginger up and carry it forward. From that moment I consider myself a self-taught person and I am afraid of nothing.

**Languages** Spanish: Native.

Catalan: Native.

**English**: Fluid. Level C2 but not certificated. **French**: Basic. Studied at High School.

German: Basic. Initiation course.